Good morning.
Hey!
Woops, sorry! I didn't see you down there.
Oh. Heh!, eh... no problem. I should really
watch where I'm going.
What are you doing down there anyway? Everyone's heading
South in a few hours.
Oh, I... I...  eh, I dropped something. Yeah, you guys go on
ahead, eh I'll follow you on.
Eh... who's this guy?
I never got your name?
It's Dougal.
Hi Dougal, my name's Lucy. This is Dick.
Hi Dick.
Come on Lucy, let's get the flock outta here.
Nice to meet you Dougal, I guess I'll see you down there!
Good Morning.
Can I have ten packs of beetle husks, five tins of hazel nut
butter, eight packs of dried elderberries,
one pot of honey,a half case of nettle tea, two doz... ten
packs of fresh poppyseed,
two tins of rose-hip syrup and a
box of fennel mash.
Oh, and how much for that plant?
Now, where to put you?
Perfect.
We'll be fine.
Plenty more rain on the way, with showers due to continue
right through to the end of...
I don't care about the accident I s...
And if you do continue to eat these worms combined of course
with regular...
We are down here in the Sunny South and just check out some
of these chicks!
Lucy?
There's nothing left.
I've gotta get out of here. But how? I can't fly. Of Course
you can fly- you're a bird.
If I stay I'll freeze to death.Or starve!
I shouldn't even be here. I should be down south with the others.
I could be on the beach with Lucy. You
don't want to end up like him!
I've gotta do it.
This is it.
Ha! I did it, I'm flying, I'm really flying!
Welcome to the sunny south!
Hey, Dougal, great to see you!
Lucy, this place, it's amazing!
Yeah, Dick and I were wondering if you were gonna make it.
Oh yeah, Dick.
Hey Dick, look who it is.
Hey Dougal!
Oh. Hey Dick. So you guys aren't...
Noooo!
Ahhhh.
Dougal, now that you're here, I wanted to ask you something.
Yeah Lucy?
Do you...  wanna go for a swim?
Swim? Hu! Eh, OK!