I can lift this bit.
I can.
You need somebody to get the other end.
No, you don't.
There's one tiny bit.
Right, we need it in that pile.
One more.
Right, let me carry it.
Put it there.
Put it over there.
Tiny bit more.
Down there, what I left.
Down there it is.
Right,
do it.
This isn't very heavy.
I cannot lift all of those at the same time.
All of those I cannot lift.
I'm driving the animal boat.
I keep, I keep their food
in here, in this little hole
And I sprinkle it out all over the floors of the boat.
The giraffes like leaves.
The lions, I think the lions like
The lions like
prowling around,
so I give them prowling around lessons.
What do you have to do?
Don't!
You lifted it!
No, I did.
Why?
What do you have to do,
what are you doing?
What are you doing?
I'm making an aeroplane.
Lunchtime?
It's lunchtime!
What is that?
An aeroplane.
Can I go in the aeroplane?
Yes,
Can I?
And we need a lift to America!
America?
Ok.
Can I just get a gearstick?
And I would like to be taken to Ben 10 World.
My place first!
And then my place.
Then your place, then your place.
I want to go to Fire Land.
Everybody sitting quietly?
Good
There's Ben 10 World.
At Batman World!
That's you at Batman World
Where do you want to go my best pal?
I want to go to Flyer World.
This is Fire World.
Where do you want to go?
Fire World?
So do you, don't you?
Actually, I don't want to
I want to go to Smoke Bloke Land.
Girls are not allowed to go to Smoke Bloke Land.
cause that's too difficult for them.
Can I go back?
I really wanted to go to America.
America?
I do too.
Right, that's you at America!
No, we haven't even drived!
Yes, we have.
No we haven't.
Yes I have.
That's you and you at America.
Then to Smoke Bloke Land!
That's you at Smoke Bloke Land.
Where do you want to go?
Fire World?
Into the middle of nowhere.
Into the middle of nowhere!
Right, you have to get on there
and you have to get on there.
That's you at nowhere.
Go get off.
Where do you want to go?
Can I be an aeroplane?
This is just an aeroplane that I built
and it's for me.
Well, can I be a
an aeroplane that can move?
This can't move.
If I be an aeroplane, can I move?
This is not a moving aeroplane.
I'll be a moving aeroplane.
What?
I move, no play aeroplane.
You can pretend to have an aeroplane.
Hello Mr. Ladybird!
A ladybird?
Yeah.
They have poisonous wee.
Who says that?
Woody and Logan.
I think,
do you think they have got poisonous poo?
No, I don't think they are telling the truth.
No, they aren't.
I'm going to tell them not to do it.