Hey!
Come on!
Stop!
That's my camera! That's my camera!
Stop them!
You bastards!
Sorry.
Thank you.
You, are the worst beach boy I know.
I am simply the best at being the worst.
I am bored.
You are often bored, Mbwana.
The same beachy, the same sun, the same life.
We need to build something in this town, no?
What we need is tourist dollars, and we won't get tourist dollars
thieving from the few Muzungu we have, eh?
The tourists we have are not good enough.
We need to change things, eh? We need to build something wild here.
Your brain is wild, Mbwana.
We need to build the Buckingham Palace.
Buckingham Palace?
Why not, eh? Get the Queen to move in and
then we can build the Eiffel Tower.
I prefer the Rag Mahal. You are too wild Mbwana.
I will kick you, I will kick you!
So you are taking pictures?
You look like one of those lesbians.
Just give me the pictures.
Delete it, delete the picture.
Okay, take it properly then.
Look at this.
That was a good one.
You look like an Italian lesbian
Let me see that one.
A Spanish lesbian, with a Drogba face.
You are jealous. Take another one.
Do you think I have a best side or are they both equally better?
I think they are both equally ugly, so it's okay!
Vogue, Vogue.
You look like a buffoon.
A baboon? I know many fine baboons.
Did you see that? Did you see that?
Juma, Juma did you take the photo?
I did. I got the picture, look at it.
Where are you going?
To make some tourist dollar!
Yes, this is quite something.
Zanzibar is fast becoming the world’s capital
in the realm of giant fish.
Thousands of tourists are making the trip and
heading to the most spectacular.
Hi everybody, raise your glasses to me, the Fish Man!
More, more, more!
Go, go, I don't need you anyway,
I'll find my way, I'll find my way home
No room for you on the bus, old man.
Quite something.
Get back!