We talked about evolution. Today we can actually see it.
Today's research in the development of life, is a
meeting of revolutionary new technologies and old issues,
because when genetic scientists looked closely
at our genes and DNA
we are starting to see it in the light of evolution
the classic issues that are starting to get answered with
the help of genetic engineering is who is related to whom.
We wish to label everything. We can see that deep down,
a whale is a swimming camel.
It's not obvious when you see it, but we have been forced
to move about a lot of branches on the tree of life.
''Furgus''
Hello?
Hey, it's me.
How are you doing?
Ok.
How was it?
Well, how did it go?
I'm gonna die.
Come on...
He won't see me anymore.
What?
Well, it's...
First, he said that he didn't have enough time.
Then he said that there wasn't enough time.
Then, he said that he's in love with another.
He has been seeing her all this time.
That sounds totally crazy!
What a fucking asshole.
Well, now they have cut down my hours,
which is not fun at all
I think he has given me a fucking venerial disease.
Come on...
I will die.
You will not die.
Yes!
No!
Yes, it itches like hell and I will die!
No, but you've probably got fungus.
I've had it and it's disgusting! It itches.
You can just get some stuff from the pharmacy.
I think I have some left. And then...
Wait.
Has she gone mad?
Who?
The old lady in number nine!
What's she doing?
She's like a hundred years old and now she's standing
completely fucking naked, just screaming!
Nude? Are you kidding?
No, I'm not.
That's sick!
What's she doing now?
Tell me!
What's she doing?
This is so weird.
Well, now they've cut down my hours
and that doesn't feel good at all.
I'm gonna die! He's given me shit.
Cut it out. You've got fungus. You just have to buy...
What's that?
Wait.
Hello?
It's me. Can you let me in? I'm just gonna grab my stuff,
the jacket and the pan. I' ll be fast.
Hello?
Katrin?
Hello, hello, hello, hello?
Hello? Hey, what's going on?
He's here.
For fuck's sake.
He's outside.
Don't let him in!
Tell him that you're not at home.
He wants his stuff back. There's an itch between my legs
and he wants his stuff back.
Toss it out from the balcony or something.
Let me in, Katrin! I know you're there, you just answered!
Hey, doesn't he owe you money?
A thousand kronor.
Did you get it back?
I'm sorry. Hey, I'm really sorry.
Last week he told me he loved me. I love him, you know.
No, I don't get it at all.
My jacket and pan.
Is it itching?
Like hell.
Yeah, well...
Katrin? What the hell is she doing?
Katrin?
Hello?
Hello, hello, hello, hello?
Answer me!
Katrin?
I'm hanging up now.
Katrin, I'm hanging up now.
Hello?
I'm hanging up now.
Hello!
Where the hell did you go?
I won't get my money back.
Well, just tell him that you want it back.
I have to go.
Come on now. It's only fungus. You're not going to die.
Just buy one of those ointments.
Perhaps.
Anyway. I have another meeting with my boss.
You know, I've been working there for five years...
the whales. Both whales and dolphins belong to a
bransch that goes out from the tree of life.
So, we follow it back so that we can see where it meets
other animals. Which animals are similar to whales?
Then we enter into what we call the ungulates.
This includes, for example,cows, pigs and camels.
Among all the other animals, whales are the closest...