I have an iron will.
to achieve the goals of a
peaceful revolution
civil nation
My house is small.
It can be hard to breathe.
So when I found that key,
I was curious.
Because I knew the key belonged to the big man
I knew it was for his big house.
I heard he was gone.
And it was true. He was gone.
The house was empty.
So I took a chance.
You would've done the same.
Let me tell you.
It's a different world inside.
He's got everything he needs.
And more.
So why shouldn't he share?
Can't he give me a little?
Aren't I a good kid?
I deserve it.
With all that space, I could breathe.
I felt like I could move.
I felt like I could fly.
Who's there?
There he is!
Get out!
But that's not my house.
And it never will be.
So where do I go?
Where can I breathe?
I guess...
there are other rooms.