Peter!
Jesus Christ.
Can you get in please?
Did you put my jacket in?
Yes.
And my skirt?
Yes. It's in the back.
Now get in, it's going to be 4½  hours
All right.
I don't feel happy about leaving the boys.
They're with your sister Alison, they will be fine.
I'd told them we'd back in time for Sunday lunch
but I don't think they believe me.
They don't believe you Alison because they are dogs.
They can't understand you.
Yes they can.
No they can't.
Peter I am with them all day.
They understand me perfectly.
Well if they understand you so well,
you can ask them to shit directly
into the plastic bag when they take them for a walk.
or better still into the bin.
Maybe they could do some pots once in a while
or mow the lawn.
Peter what is wrong with you today?
Is it your toenail thing?
No, it's not the townail thing.
I don't see why we have to rush down there today
they're not getting married until tomorrow.
I told you 3 months ago this was the plan.
We're going up on Friday night
because we're meeting them in the pub.
I'm going to miss my Saturday morning lengths.
Everyone is meeting in the pub this evening (who is everyone?),
pre-wedding drinks.
We're meeting The Gang,
you know I used to
Tooty's Gang?
It wasn't her gang, it was just people
I was used to hang out with at university.
You don't hang out with them much anymore.
Of course I do, we had Christmas drinks
with Davey in that pub.
Who?
Davey
The fat man in the rugby shirt?
Yes.
The one who fell over the pregnant woman.
He didn't fall.
He's ghastly.
He was off balance.
He was drinking whisky.
Yes, well that's not a crime, is it?
Well, we should check into the B&b first.
What?
We have to check into the B&b first.
Why are you saying like that?
I'm not saying like that.
You are.
I'm not.
Weird.
"B&b".
Yes, that's what I said.
Bed & Breakfast.
B&b.
Not a "B&b, a "B&B".
B&b, it's like A&e.
What's that got to do with?
Well it's like P&o.
What?
Or D&g.
What's that?
Oh P I'm literally getting married tomorrow.
I know.
Cigarello?
It's been an age, but go on.
Tell. Me. Everything.
Well, there's not much to tell…
How's Alice?
Very well actually, she's good.
It's Alison.
Toots I lost my job.
Poor P.
A couple of months ago. Alison doesn't know.
It's quite funny I've just been hanging
around in Hyde Park in the day.
You'll find another
Yeah, well, I've got this meeting
with Alan Teasdale, next week.
I'm really hoping that comes through because, if it doesn't
I'm going to be in a bit of a pickle, you know, mortgage people
I can't believe I am actually getting married tomorrow!
Yeah, I know.
Do you remember at university
we used to do this all the time?
Yeah, I know, we went to that pub, The Plough,
do you remember?
You used to smoke indoors then,
this feels really naughty.
It is naughty.
It's really naughty.
Do you remember when we were really, really naughty?
You know, I can't believe I only got to fuck you once.
Peter!
Hi Alice, you look nice.
Are you smoking?
No.
Yes.
Why are you standing like that?
I need the loo. So…
Peter, when are we going to check-in at the B&b?
That's Davey.
Look, I need to use the credit card.
You've got your one haven't you?
Yeah but it's not working.
Why not?
Well, I don't know. I can't phone them and ask.
Yes you can it's 24 hour, or India,
that's awake now…
I bought a round so I need to pay for it.
How much is it? I've got some money.
It's... £486.
What!?
Look, I offered to buy the meal as well, because...
Why?
Well, because it's the gang isn't it?
It's the university gang and I
Peter!
It's what you do.
It's a lot of money.
Just please give me the card.
It's supposed to be for emergencies only.
Stupid.
What's the PIN number?
It's my birthday.
Peter, it's four days after our wedding anniversary.
Alison. I think it's time to switch the light out.
I'm reading my book.
You've been reading that book for about 7 months.
It's quite a complicated story
You're on page 23 or something.
Do you remember Toulouse?
Do you remember what we did?
It is lights out.
Sorry, sorry.
Shall I take these off Mademoiselle?
That's nice.
What have we here?
Wait! Wait! Wait!
I can't! I can't!
Is this because of Tooty?
Sorry, I'm sorry
That's OK.
You're on my arm.
Sorry.
Goodnight.
You OK?
Sorry. Sorry.
Don't be sorry.
What's wrong?
It's nothing, it's stupid. Stupid Peter, he's stupid
Right.
He's been dirty dancing with Tooty all evening.
Would he dance with me? No.
Well, he's a fool, isn't he?
I asked him if he'd put my skirt in the car and he said he had.
But he hadn't.
I think it looks fine with the jeans.
Thank you.
I've got an idea. I'm Aiden by the way.
Alison.
That's a lovely name.
Is it?
Listen Alison, what I like to do when I'm a little bit upset,
is just go to my car and relax.
I just like to relax.
Me too.
Really?
Do want to come with me and relax?
In my car?
Yes.
Cool. Follow me.
Hey Toots.
Hi P.
No, no, no.
I just thought you'd want a drink.
Oh, shit, sorry.
Cheers!
Cheers.
Listen, no, no, no Toots, listen.
I've got a really serious thing that I've gotta say,
cos I've been thinking about this
sort of for a long time, actually a lot today.
And I just wanted to say that I love you.
Aaahh I love you to P.
No listen to me.
I love you and I've loved you ever since I first met you.
You know what, we could go now couldn't we?
Pete what are you doing?
No c'mon we could do that!
Look I don't have much but we could go.
I really don't have much because unless Alan Teasdale
comes good next week I am fucked.
I am totally fucked.
But Pete, you're really drunk, seriously.
I'm drunk on love OK.
I'm drunk on love for you
I love Doug, I've just married Doug.
Doug!? C'mon!
So yesterday in the pub and you were on me and I was on you…
Listen you know that we could have sex right now.
And I know that's what you want because I want it too,
so let's just go and do that now.
My cousin has a pace in Dorset, or Devon, but I could phone him.
Peter! It's Doug. It's Doug
Oooo It's Doug! I'm in the army! I'm Doug! I'm Brilliant!
The things is the Moroccans, they know how to deal with stress.
I'm the same as you, I get stressed out at weddings.
Weddings are always the same. People having arguments about this and that.
You've just to get Moroccan about it and that suits me
because I like the Moroccan stuff.
Jesus Christ!
Teach them.
I'm gay.
I’m gay.
I have been thinking about it for a while
and I've realised I'm definitely gay.
It’s just that you said about relaxing in the car.
I meant smoking a spliff.
I didn't mean...
getting fresh.
Is it my breasts have they turned you gay?
No!
They're very nice.
Thank you.
If I had to rate them out of 10.
I'd say.
6?
Definitely, definitely 7.
That's quite good isn't it?
Yup.
My hairdresser is gay I think.
He's called Craig.
I lost my job Alison.
I know.
Tooty told me last night.
After she told me you'd had sex together back
when you were in your Gang.
But you should know.
Last night a man told me my breasts were a 7
which is actually quite high.
I rang the dogs
told them we'd be back by lunchtime.
Did they ask us to pick anything up?
Don't be stupid Peter. They're dogs.
If you just
Not a word.